{
  "chapter": 19,
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the cloud deployments provides most economical services?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Public cloud",
        "Hybrid cloud",
        "Private cloud",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Metering falls under which category of cloud service management?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Business support",
        "Provisioning and configuration",
        "Portability and interoperability",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Billing falls under which category of cloud service management?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Business support",
        "Provisioning and configuration",
        "Portability and interoperability",
        "None of these"
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Vendor-neutral cloud infrastructure management tool can be possible through the standardizations of",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cloud services",
        "Cloud providers",
        "Infrastructure management APIs",
        "All of these"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "CIMI-specified standardized APIs are associated with which level of services?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IaaS", "PaaS", "SaaS", "IDaaS"],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Service management responsibility of consumer is least at the layer of",
      "incorrect_answers": ["IaaS", "PaaS", "SaaS", "DBaaS"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The number of phases present in cloud lifecycle management is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["5", "6", "4", "10"],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The number of phases present in SLA lifecycle management is",
      "incorrect_answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Data backup for recovery in cases of disaster should be maintained for which type(s) of data?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fixed data",
        "Transient data",
        "Configuration data",
        "Persistent data"
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which among the following models is not a supported programming model of Aneka cloud?",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MapReduce programming",
        "Filter programming",
        "Task programming",
        "Thread programming"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    }
  ]
}
